[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What plastic toy, invented by George Lerner in 1949, has the distinction of being the first toy advertised on television?", "correct_answer": "Mr. Potato Head", "incorrect_answers": ["Raggedy Ann Doll", "Barbie", "Mrs. Potato Head"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What phobia means fear of making decisions?", "correct_answer": "Decidophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Deipnophobia", "Defecaloesiophobia", "Dementophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lactose is a type of sugar consisting of two subunits (galactose and glucose), found primarily in what food?", "correct_answer": "Milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Fruits", "Vegetables", "Honey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the diet of elephants mostly consist of?", "correct_answer": "Grasses", "incorrect_answers": ["Leaves", "Twigs", "Tree bark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You should stir the rice while frying it until it becomes this.", "correct_answer": "Translucent", "incorrect_answers": ["White", "Soft", "Golden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1994 film, Pulp Fiction, these actors portray Jules Winfield and Vincent  Vega.", "correct_answer": "Samuel L. Jackson and John Travolta", "incorrect_answers": ["Ving Rhames and John Travolta", "Bruce Willis and Phil Lamarr", "Ving Rhames and Samuel L. Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tzatziki is a typical dip of this country. It is made with yogurt, olive oil, cucumbers and onions.", "correct_answer": "Greece", "incorrect_answers": ["Montenegro", "Turkey", "Romania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The English poet William Blake wrote two beautiful poems concerning what two animals?", "correct_answer": "The tiger and the lamb", "incorrect_answers": ["The fox and the chickens", "The elephant and the mouse", "The lion and the lamb"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the director of the award-winning films Antonias Line, The Luzhin Defense, and Mrs. Dalloway?", "correct_answer": "Marleen Gorris", "incorrect_answers": ["Julie dash", "Josee Dayan", "Nikki Caro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If police catch a graffiti offender and they are under 18, the parents will have to pay a fine, up to this amount.", "correct_answer": "$ 10 000", "incorrect_answers": ["$ 20 000", "$ 100 000", "$ 5 000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Color Purple, what happens to Miss Celies son and daughter?", "correct_answer": "They were adopted and lived in Africa.", "incorrect_answers": ["They were stillborn.", "She never had children.", "They both left home to attend college."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Arterial blood is blue due to oxygenation. Venous blood is bright red and spurts when a person receives a cut.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]